welcome to category five technology TV
欢迎来到五类科技电视
this is episode number 544 so nice to
这是第544集 很好看
have you here this week we've got an
本周有你在这里，我们有一个
exciting show planned for you if all
精彩呈现计划适合 你 ，如果所有
goes well we're gonna show you how to
我们会告诉你如何去做
install plex media server on a little
稍微安装plex媒体服务器
Raspberry Pi 3 it's like a micro
树莓派3 它就像一个微型
computer that fits in the palm of my
电脑，适合我的手掌
hand if I had a shirt pocket I could put
如果我有一个衬衫口袋， 我可以放
it in there it's so tiny we're gonna
它在那里很小， 我们会去的
learn how to set up our own would be
学习如何 建立自己的会是
kind of homebrew Netflix on that device
该设备上的一种自制的Netflix
this is gonna be cool stick around
这 将是很酷的棒
this is category 5 technology TV
这是第 5 类 技术电视
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]
our live recordings are trusted only to
我们的现场录音是值得信赖的只有
solid-state drive by Kingston Technology
金士顿科技的固态硬盘
revive your computer with improved
通过改进来恢复您的计算机
performance and reliability over
性能和可靠性 上
traditional hard drives with Kingston
传统硬盘与 金士顿
SSDs category 5 TV streams live with
固态硬盘5类电视流与现场直播
Telestream Wirecast and nimble streamer
Telestream Wirecast和灵活的流光
tune in every week on roku Kodi Plex and
每周在roku Kodi Plex和
other HLS video players for local show
本地演出的其他HLS视频播放器
times that category 5 TV category 5 TV
次5 类电视 5 类电视
is a member of the tech podcast network
是科技播客网络的成员
if it's tech it's here cat 5 TV slash
如果 它是高科技它在这里 的猫5 TV 斜杠
TPN and the International Association of
TPN 和 国际协会
internet broadcasters cat 5 TV slash ia
互联网广播公司猫5电视 斜杠ia
IB
IB
welcome to the show this is category 5
欢迎来到这个展会，这是第 5 类
technology TV so nice to have you here
技术电视真高兴能有你在这里
Sasha's back yeah way last week did you
Sasha 上周 回到了 你的方式
have a nice week I had a great week good
祝你有个美好的一周，我有一个美好的一周
good I spent my that that day yes it's
好， 我那天度过了那一天， 是 的
not Valentine's Day I booked my
不是情人节那天我订了我的
honeymoon
度蜜月
hey nice near future I'll have another
嘿好的不久的将来我会有另一个
week there you go what are you doing
一周你去你在做什么
we're going to Dominican nice I know all
我们要多明尼加不错，我知道 所有
of our viewers from the Dominican give
我们的观众来自多米尼加
us a whoop-whoop yes please come see me
我们是一个呐喊， 是的 请来看看我
well no maybe not it's my honeymoon
好吧，不，也许不是我的蜜月
I'd actually happily host on the resort
我真的很乐意主持这个度假胜地
you can get date passes see yes there
你 可以得到日期 通行证 在那里看到是的
you go okay so this is coming up that's
你好， 所以这 是即将到来的
coming up in March
三月即将到来
nice yes they're gonna have a week off
很好， 他们会休息一周
and I'm gonna have to find someone to
我必须找人去
fill in for you
为你 填写
yes Jeff is away today that's yeah so
是的， 杰夫今天就是这样的
it's just us last week Becca was here
上周 贝卡就在这里
thank you everyone for your kind remarks
谢谢大家 的亲切评论
and all the thumbs up that we got on
以及我们所得到的所有赞扬
YouTube as well we've been doing you
YouTube 以及我们一直在 做 你
know growing our audience on YouTube
知道在YouTube上增长我们的观众
because it's been a process for us
因为这 对我们来说 是一个过程
because we're predominantly on like on
因为我们主要是喜欢
cable TV and on roku and Kody and Plex
有线电视， roku和Kody和Plex
and platforms like set-top boxes and
和机顶盒等平台
Smart TVs and so our audience is not
智能电视， 所以我们的观众不是
predominantly on YouTube right
主要在YouTube 上
and those who do watch on YouTube
和那些在YouTube上观看的人
possibly don't have accounts or maybe
可能没有帐户或可能
don't comment and things like that so we
不要评论和这样的事情， 所以我们
really appreciate you becoming a part of
真的很感激你成为的一部分
that community as well watching our show
该社区以及 观看我们的节目
is watching our clips on on YouTube we
正在观看我们在YouTube上的剪辑
have not only category 5 TV but every
不仅有 5 类 电视，而且每个电视都有
week we added up the show into
我们把节目加进去了
itty-bitty bite-sized pieces right those
itty-小小的一口大小的块的权
go on Linux tech show and so you can do
继续Linux技术展会，所以你可以做
the search for that on YouTube or you
在YouTube或你的搜索
can just go Linux tech show comm and
可以去Linux 技术展通信和
your favorite browser and it will
你最喜欢的浏览器，它会
automatically redirect you there it's
自动将您重定向到那里
cool because sometimes like this is an
很酷， 因为有时候就像这样
hour-plus show the full the full episode
小时以上 显示 完整剧集
but then the features themselves may be
但是这些功能本身 可能是
between 5 and 20 minutes long exactly so
5 至20分钟长的时间恰好 如此
people say in the comments hey how come
人们在 评论中 说 嘿怎么回事
I had to wait for 45 minutes to get them
我不得不等待45 分钟才能得到它们
to the meat of this over to Linux tech
到的这种 过度到Linux高科技肉
show duck right exactly then you'll be
显示鸭子正确的时候你会
able to watch just those little itty
能够看到那些小小的 东西
bitty snippets these funny YouTube
这些有趣的YouTube 小片段
people yeah and everything that I just
人是啊 ，我只是一切
said will be cut out you will never hear
说将被切断 ，你永远不会听到
this if you're on I have been saying to
这如果你在我一直在说
all of my friends lately whenever I'm
所有我的朋友， 无论我什么时候
talking about cat 5 I say check check us
谈论猫5我说检查 检查我们
out on YouTube first and then all over
在YouTube上，然后再全
the rest o or Plex or Roku or Co kvv be
其余的o或Plex或Roku或Co kvv都可以
hello California and all the ways that
你好加利福尼亚州和所有的方式
you can catch the show cool California
你可以捕捉到 酷炫的 加州
story yes one of the patients I work at
故事是 我工作 的 病人 之一
a chiropractic clinic and one of the
一家脊骨疗法诊所和其中一家
patients there is a truck driver and she
病人有一名卡车司机 和她
drives through California oh yeah yes I
开车穿过加利福尼亚 噢，是的，我
wonder if she's seen our billboard
想知道她是否看过我们的广告牌
exactly so there you go I I think
正是如此，你去我认为
there's a picture of Jeff giving you the
有 一张杰夫给你的照片
the bunny ears up on one of those
兔子耳朵在其中之一
billboards somewhere in Southern
南部某处的广告牌
California look for it take a picture
加利福尼亚州找它拍照
and send it to us let me know exactly
并发 送给我们 让我确切地知道
where it is yeah that would be cool yes
那里是的，那会很酷
we've got a fantastic show planned for
我们有一个精彩的 节目计划
you tonight we're gonna be looking at
你今晚我们会看着
how to get plex media server up and
如何获得Plex媒体服务器和
running on a Raspberry Pi 3
运行在Raspberry Pi 3上
I don't want to talk too much about it
我不想谈论太多
before the break we're gonna cover it
在 休息 之前 我们会覆盖它
right after this so stick around and
右后这个如此坚持围绕 和
it's gonna be fun yes it's gonna be fun
它会很有趣，它会 很有趣
it's gonna be a blast here we go you've
这会是一个 爆炸这里我们去你已经
got mad skills
疯狂的技能
now hone them learn new skills or
现在磨练他们学习新技能或
improve your existing ones with online
通过在线改进现有 的
video tutorials and training from
视频教程和培训
lynda.com through our special link at
lynda.com通过我们的特别链接
cat5 dot TV slash Linda learned software
cat5 dot 电视剧斜线 琳达学习 软件
technology creative and business skills
技术创意和 商业技能
you can use today to help you achieve
你可以 使用今天 来帮助你实现
your professional goals join today and
你的职业目标今天 加入
start learning we'll give you this
开始学习， 我们会给你这个
chance to try it absolutely free with
有机会尝试它 完全免费
unlimited access to all of the courses
无限制地访问所有 的课程
sign up now for free cat5 dot TV slash
现在注册免费的 cat5点 电视斜线
Linda welcome back this is category 5
琳达欢迎回来，这是第5类
technology TV and imagine that in this
技术电视和想象在这
little box is a server huh this is the
小盒子是服务器呵呵这是
world that we live in a Raspberry Pi 3
我们住 在Raspberry Pi 3的世界
you can pick them up at camp 5 dot TV
你可以在营地 5点电视上 接他们
slash PI it'll direct you to all kinds
削减PI它会引导你到各种
of sources like you can buy them on
像你这样的消息来源可以买到
Amazon you've got one I have one I've
亚马逊你有我拥有的一个
got several mm a lot of us have several
有几个 毫米 ，我们 很多 人有几个
but they're an inexpensive SBC any guess
但他们是一个廉价的SBC任何 猜测
on what SBC stands for SBC yeah put me
关于SBC代表SBC是什么让我
on the spot hmm
当场嗯
okay like super super bitty computer
好像超级 超级小电脑
sync single board computer very close so
同步单板电脑非常接近所以
it's like the size of a credit card and
它就像一张 信用卡 的大小和
it is all built into one circuit board
它全部内置于一个电路板中
right so the processor the RAM
正确的处理器的RAM
everything is in there the only thing
一切都在那里唯一的东西
that you have to really add is you've
你必须 真正添加的是你
got to put it in a case which I've done
必须把它放在我已经完成的案例中
here you all can you can kind of see
在这里你可以看到所有人
that under my monitor there it is super
在我的显示器下面，它超级
easy to build I did don't want in an
容易建立我不想在一个
episode episode yeah
情节插曲耶
previously we've done a lot of rat
以前我们做过 很多 老鼠
berry pie features and last week was no
浆果馅饼的功能和上周没有
exception we did the comparison of the
我们做了 比较的 例外
ex u4q to the raspberry pi 3 in past
前u4q 在 过去 的树莓派 3
episodes sashes built one go on to our
情节边框建立了一个去 我们的
website category 5 dot TV and click on
网站类别5点电视和点击
the search up at the top you'll be able
在顶部搜索就可以了
to just type in raspberry pi and you'll
只需键入树莓派，你就会
find a bunch of stuff I put that right
找到一堆我 把它 的 东西
there just to remind you what we're
那只是为了提醒你我们是什么
talking about speaking of having done
谈论说完成了
raspberry pi features in the past yes
覆盆子pi的功能在过去是的
episode number 4 59 Jeff and I were on
第4集第59集杰夫和我在上
the air you were in the newsroom and we
你在 新闻编辑室和我们 的空气
did the very same feature that we're
做了和我们一样的功能
doing tonight however things have
但是 今晚做了 事情
changed things have changed episode 4 59
改变的事情改变了第4集 59
that was almost two years ago right and
这几乎是两年前的 权利和
in that time now that demonstration was
那个时候现在这个示范是
on Debbie and Jesse raspy and Jesse in
在Debbie和Jesse raspy和Jesse在
this case and now we're using raspy and
这种情况下，现在我们正在使用raspy和
stretch so we've had a really great
伸展， 所以我们有一个 非常棒的
response and if you're watching this on
反应，如果你正在看 这个
youtube you know that you you may have
youtube你知道 你可能有
found this through our previous feature
通过我们以前的功能找到了这个
from two years ago and now being 2018 a
从两年前，现在到2018年a
lot of the technology has changed it's
很多技术已经改变了它
improved it's gotten better and it's
改善它变得更好，这是
also broken some of the steps in the
也破坏了一些步骤
tutorial from our video from a couple
来自我们夫妇视频的教程
years back right so high time for us to
多年的 时间 让我们 度过 这么高的时间
redo the demonstration refresher and
重做示范进修
show you how to do it sascha one of the
告诉你如何做到这一点 sascha之一
things that has changed since that
自那之后发生了变化
initial demonstration is we've been
最初的演示是我们一直在做的
watching the comments on YouTube we've
观看我们YouTube上 的 评论
been watching the comments on our
一直在看我们 的 评论
website category 5 TV and one of the
网站类别 5电视 和其中之一
rezoning comments
重新分区评论
well basically one of the resounding
基本上是一个响亮的
themes is coming from people who are
主题来自谁是谁
brand-new to single board computing
全新的单板计算
brand-new to Linux and they want to try
全新的Linux ，他们想尝试
it out but it's so complicated to go
它， 但它是如此 复杂去
through all these steps yes this is kind
通过所有这些步骤是的，这是善良的
of a two piece demonstration in this one
在这一个两块示范
video we're gonna get to the DIY let's
视频我们会去 DIY的让我们
break it down and walk you through all
分解它，并引导你通过所有
the steps step by step
一步 一步的步骤
show you how to set up your own
告诉你如何建立 你自己的
Raspberry Pi plex media server but we've
树莓派Plex媒体服务器，但我们已经
also taken the time to create a ready to
也花时间 创建一个准备好
deploy image for Raspberry Pi 3
为Raspberry Pi 3部署映像
it's called Plex Pi and you can get a
它叫做Plex Pi， 你可以得到一个
duplex pi
双面pi
komm I think that you're very lucky that
komm 我认为你很 幸运
I am the co-host today because if you
今天 我是 共同主持人，因为如果 你
are a brand new user I have the right
是一个全新的用户， 我有权利
question she's got the questions for us
问题她对我们有问题
such as what is plaques it's what it
如什么是 它的斑块
starts with right folks
从正确的人开始
yeah the bare minimum question going
是的最低限度的问题会
into a demonstration of how to create a
演示如何创建 一个
plex server is what is Plex what is Plex
Plex服务器是什么Plex什么是Plex
plex media server think of it this way
Plex媒体服务器就是这样想的
Jeff and I like to call it our home brew
杰夫和我喜欢把 它 称为 我们的 家酿
Netflix take all of your videos put them
Netflix 把 你 所有 的 视频都放进去
on a drive o take all of your you know
在驱动器O 以你的所有，你知道
the part of the video podcasts that you
视频 播客 的一部分 ，你
watch like category 5 TV if you download
如果您下载，请观看类别5电视
our torrents put them on that drive put
我们的种子把它们放在那个 驱动器 上
them into a folder and plug it into plex
他们到一个文件夹， 并将其插入丛
then plex media server in our case on a
那么plex媒体服务器就在我们的情况下了
Raspberry Pi 3 creates an environment
树莓派3创造一个环境
that looks and feels a lot like Netflix
看起来 和Netflix很像
it keeps track of what episodes you've
它会跟踪你的剧集
seen it allows you to rate episodes it
看到它可以让你评分剧集
shows you the description and a
向您显示说明和a
thumbnail image of each episode in each
每个 插曲的缩略图图像
movie and as you watch things it it
电影，当你看着它的事情
marks them as watched so if you're
将他们标记为已观看，如果你是
watching something like category 5 TV
看着类似5电视的东西
and there are 11 seasons of this thing
这东西有11个季节
right you can actually see where you've
对， 你实际上可以 看到你的位置
gotten to so if you're binge watching
如果你喜欢看电影，那么你就会这么做
anything it makes it really easy ok same
任何它使得它可以很容易 确定相同
with like in the middle of an episode
就像在一集中
like you can turn it off and then you
就像你可以把它关掉 然后 你
come back to later and it's in the right
回来后 ，它是在正确的
spot then the other nice thing about
然后发现另一件好事
plex media server along that vein is
沿着该静脉的多媒体服务器是
that it works with all your devices so
它适用于 所有的设备 ，以便
oh this device will be plugged into your
哦，这个设备将被插入你的
TV no doubt and you'll be streaming
电视毫无疑问，你会流
video directly on the device but then if
视频直接在设备上， 但如果
you have an Ethernet cable plugged into
你有一根以太网电缆插入
it you can be using your tablet and
它可以使用您的平板电脑和
watching it on your tablet you can have
看着它在平板电脑上，你可以 有
you can have it on your computer
你可以在你的电脑上 安装它
upstairs or the TV in the living room or
楼上或 客厅里 的电视机 或
the bedroom and still and not have to
卧室和仍然不必
move the device around it streams it
移动设备周围 的直播
through your network to any of your
通过你的网络到你的任何一个
devices through the web browser can it
设备通过网页浏览器 就可以了
be multi-use okay within the limitations
在限制范围内 多用 可以
of a Raspberry Pi because it is a very
树莓派， 因为它是一个非常
small micro server it doesn't have the
小型微型服务器它没有
same amount of power as a supercomputer
超级计算机 的功率 相同
but yes you can you can definitely
但是，你可以绝对可以
string
串
to multiple devices so if you're
多个 设备，所以如果你是
watching it on your TV downstairs mm-hmm
在楼下看电视 - 嗯
and you pause it because it's time to
你暂停一下，因为是时候 了
make supper you go up to the kitchen you
让晚饭去 你 的厨房
pull out your Android tablet or your
取出你的Android 平板电脑或 你的
phone and you set it up and you push
电话，你设置 它，你推
play it starts right where you left off
播放它从你离开的地方开始
while you were downstairs that's a
而你在楼下的 那是一个
magnificent homebrew Netflix with your
宏伟的 自制Netflix与你的
own content works with home movies works
自己的内容适用于家庭电影作品
with mp3s and your music library and it
与MP3 和您的音乐 库和 它
plays web streaming we have an actual
播放网络流媒体我们有一个实际的
plex channel an add-on that you can put
Plex频道 您可以放置​​的附加组件
into your plex deployment and it gives
进入您的 plex部署，并提供
you access to all of our back episodes
你可以访问我们所有的 后面 章节
plus live streaming during the live
加上现场直播
broadcast so it is very well-rounded
广播， 所以它是非常 全面的
solution and we're gonna learn how to
解决方案，我们将学习 如何
set that up on a PI perfect why why
把它设置在一个 完美的 原因为什么
would we do this
我们会这样做吗？
why would why do we ever use a Raspberry
为什么我们会使用树莓
Pi 3 because they're amazing they are
丕3，因为他们是惊人的 ，他们是
amazing they're inexpensive and they are
令人惊叹的是他们价格便宜，而且他们是
very inexpensive sacha they are easy not
非常便宜的sacha他们很容易 没有
only easy to use but easy to procure yes
只是易于使用，但易于 购买是的
and I may not have and you may not have
我可能没有， 你可能 没有
a server at home that has HDMI output
家中有HDMI输出的服务器
and can fit behind your TV that's
并且可以放在你的 电视机 后面
mounted on the wall this you can just
安装在墙上这个你可以 只
tape onto the back of the TV and plug an
将胶带放在电视机背面 并插上
HDMI cable in and the power cable and
HDMI电缆和 电源线
you're done right this is a very easy
你做对了这是一个非常简单的
like it's a palatable beginning step
就像这是一个可口的开始步骤
right like I feel like that like if you
就像我觉得就像 你一样
are new to all things Linux if you're
如果你是Linux的所有东西都是新手
new to all things tech and your this is
新技术的所有东西，这是你的
the first episode you've ever seen
你见过的第一集
you're lucky because this is a great
你很幸运， 因为这太棒了
first step all right all right
第一步 没事没事
so speaking of first step for those of
所以谈到那些的第一步
you who do not want to do it yourself
你不想自己做
comes Plex PI right Plex PI comm will
来自Plex PI正确的Plex PI comm
take you to well currently it just takes
目前只需带你到目前为止
you to a forum and I'm gonna bring it up
你到一个论坛，我会 提出它
on my computer screen for you I've got
在我的电脑屏幕上 给你我
my laptop here and let's just see if I
我的笔记本在这里，让 我 看看 我是否
can bring it up see if that comes up yes
可以提起来看看是否 会出现是的
okay so Plex PI comm and when I go there
好Plex PI comm，当我去那里
right now we haven't built a website for
现在我们还没有建立一个 网站
it yet it just takes you to the category
它只是把你带到这个类别
five community forum and you'll see a
五个社区论坛，你会看到一个
development forum here because it is
发展论坛，因为它是
under development right now
正在开发的现在
and if you scroll there are three sticky
如果你滚动有三个粘性
posts one of them is introduction to
其中一篇是介绍
Plex PI and download Plex PI images and
Plex PI 并下载Plex PI图像和
when you go there there's a brief
当你去 那里时有一个简短的介绍
introduction as to how it works how to
介绍它是 如何 工作的
follow along with the steps and of
按照步骤 和
course where you can download it as well
当然你也可以下载 它
and this is going to evolve over time we
而这 会随着时间的推移，我们
are going to create a website at plex pi
将在plex pi上创建一个网站
comm so that it's you know more
让你知道更多
attractive and easier to find what
有吸引力，更容易找到什么
you're looking for
您正在寻找
but in the meantime it gives you free
但在此期间，它给你免费
access to the image so what that means
访问图像，这是什么意思
is for those who don't want to do it
对于 那些 不想 做 谁
yourself if you're not a Linux guru and
你自己 如果你不是一个 Linux大师和
you don't want to go through the steps
你不想经过这些步骤
and figure it out and follow along with
并且弄清楚 ，并请跟随
the steps that we're gonna show you
我们要 告诉你 的步骤
tonight you can just fire up this image
今晚 你可以开启这张 图片
use something like etcher that's the
使用像etcher这样的东西
program that I like to use right so you
程序， 我喜欢 用你的权利
install etcher
安装蚀刻机
I've got a link below if you're watching
如果你正在观看，我有一个链接
this on youtube or on our website or
这在 YouTube或 我们的网站 或
anywhere where we've got comments and
任何地方我们有评论 和
things follow the link to enter and that
事情遵循链接 进入和
will allow you to burn the image to a
将允许您 将图像刻录到
USB flash drive or in this case a micro
USB 闪存 驱动器或在这种情况下一个微型
SD card that you're gonna put in your
SD卡，你会把 你的
Raspberry Pi right once it's in there we
树莓派的权利 ，一旦它在那里，我们
can put it up you ready okay let's turn
可以把它准备好你准备好了，让我们开始吧
on our Raspberry Pi 3 so this is
我们的树莓派 3，所以这 是
happening in real time and I've already
发生在 实时和 我已经
burned the image for Plex PI 1.1 the
烧毁了Plex PI 1.1的图像
current version on my on my Raspberry Pi
目前版本在我的Raspberry Pi上
3 so here we go
3我们走吧
so from downloading and burning it to
所以从下载和燃烧到
now booting it for the first time it is
现在第一次启动它
this easy to get up and running with
这很容易起床和运行
Plex so you see the the raspbian desktop
Plex让你看到raspbian桌面
there now wait for it wait for it and
现在等待它等待 它 和
wait a little X is a load and you're
等一下X是一个负载，你是
gonna leave this thing running on your
会让这件事情在你身上运行
TV you're gonna fire it up and it's just
电视，你会发射它，它只是
gonna be running connected to your TV
将 与您的电视连接
you don't have to wait for it and things
你不必 等待它和事情
like that
像那样
and then we're gonna be up on the screen
然后我们会在 屏幕上
here where it's gonna ask us how do you
在这里它 会问我们你怎么样
want to login now how do you want to
现在 要 登陆你怎么 想
sign up that is a fully functional plex
注册 这是一个功能齐全的丛
media server from Plex PI com it's ready
Plex PI com的媒体服务器已准备就绪
to go
去
we just booted it up there exactly how
我们刚刚在那里启动了它
you're gonna see it so you need to sign
你会看到它，所以你需要签署
up for an account I use my email address
为 我 的 帐户 使用我的 电子邮件地址
to sign up and just like any sign up
注册并像任何注册一样
you just give them your email address
你只要给他们你的电子邮件地址
and enter a password and that is what
并输入密码 ，那是什么
you're going to use on all of your
你会 用在你所有的
devices to connect to your plex media
设备连接到您的plex媒体
server and you can access it from
服务器，你可以从中访问它
outside of your network if you've got
如果你有的话 ， 你的网络 之外
high-speed internet those kinds of
高速互联网 这些种类
things are all possible this is not a
事情都是可能的，这不是一个
tutorial on how to use plex media server
教程介绍如何 使用Plex Media Server
that's happening next week but what
这是在下周发生的， 但是什么
we're doing here is showing you how to
我们在这里做的是向 你 展示如何
get set up with a plex media server on
使用 Plex媒体服务器进行设置
your Raspberry Pi so there it is it's as
你的树莓派，所以它就是 这样
simple as that that's Plex PI comm from
就像那是Plex PI comm一样简单
there if you want to get out of it you
那里如果你想摆脱它你
hit alt f4 that takes you right into
击中ALT F4，带你进入
your regular like desktop mm-hm
你经常喜欢桌面 mm-hm
and you can just shut her down just like
你可以像关闭她一样
that ok done and now we've got an
好的 ，现在我们已经有了
opportunity to change the card I've
有机会 改变我的卡
already created a raspbian stretch
已经创造了一个raspbian舒展
installation here so for those of you
安装此所以对于那些 你
who are interested in DIY here it is
谁在 这里感兴趣的DIY
it's just raspy and stretch nothing has
它只是饶舌而且没有任何延伸
been done to it it's out-of-the-box
已经完成 它它是 开箱即用的
ready to go we're gonna learn how to
准备 去我们要去学习如何
create how to build how to install
创建如何构建如何安装
everything we need to have this become
我们需要的一切都 变成了现实
that we're going to check that out right
那我们要检查 出右
after the break stick around
在 休息之后 坚持下去
[Music]
[音乐]
Jeff Weston Jemma
杰夫韦斯顿 Jemma
you're building a brand-new beautiful
你正在建造一个 全新的美丽
website what aren't you you're terrible
网站你不是什么可怕的
actor
演员
what this where acting comes into play I
这是什么地方的演技发挥作用的我
don't know you're supposed to act okay
不知道你 应该表现得好
are you building a really cool website
你在建立一个 非常酷的网站 吗？
just because Jeff is confused doesn't
只是因为杰夫困惑 不了
mean you have to be visit cap five dot
意味着你必须访问第五点
TV slash dream host to sign up for
电视剧斜线 梦主持人 报名参加
unlimited web hosting for your website
无限网站托管为 您的网站
with unlimited email accounts MySQL
与无限的电子邮件帐户MySQL
databases the latest version of PHP
数据库是最新版本的PHP
WordPress and more and even a free
WordPress和更多，甚至 是免费的
domain name registration it's less than
域名注册是小于
six dollars per month so sign up today
每月六美元， 所以今天报名
cat five dot TV slash DreamHost
猫五点 电视斜线 DreamHost
[Music]
[音乐]
and we're back with raspbian stretch on
我们又回到了拉斯维加斯
category five technology TV now
现在五级技术电视
everything that's gonna happen from here
一切都会从 这里 发生
on out is for the DIY wanna do it
出来 是为了DIY想做
yourself and we're gonna install set up
你自己，我们将 安装设置
Plex Media Server on this bare-bones
Plex媒体服务器在此基础上
Raspberry Pi 3 if that's not you if
树莓派3如果这不是你，如果
you're not the DIY just rewind this
你不是DIY 只是回顾一下
video learn all about flex Pi calm
视频学习所有关于 flex Pi的冷静
forget about everything you're about to
忘记一切 你即将
see here today that's right we're gonna
今天在这里看到这是对的， 我们会
get real geeky here we're gonna get into
在这里得到真正的怪胎我们会进入
the Linux terminal and we're gonna see
Linux 终端 ，我们会看到
how we can get this set up so let's do
我们如何能得到这个 设置 ，以便让我们做
it okay alright so speaking of Linux
它没关系，所以说到 Linux
terminal we're gonna bring it up there
终端，我们要把它带到那里
we go and we're gonna go sudo apt update
我们走了，我们要去sudo更新
that's the first thing we want to do on
这是我们想要做的第一件事
Linux to make sure that things as far as
Linux确保事物尽可能地
our repositories are up to date now do
我们的资料库是最新的 ，现在 做
we know what a repository is a
我们知道存储库是什么
repository is something that Linux uses
存储库是Linux使用的
in order to install software
为了安装软件
it's a place on the web where a bunch of
这是一个网络上的一个地方， 一堆
software resides and anytime we want
软件驻留和 我们随时要
software all we have to do is use that
我们所需要做的就是使用软件
apt command here on raspbian or a debian
apt在这里命令raspbian或debian
derivative and then it will download it
衍生品，然后它会下载它
and install it we don't have to find
并安装它， 我们 不必 找到
their website we don't have to compile
他们的网站 我们不需要编译
anything we don't have to figure it out
任何我们不必弄清楚的地方
it's all there for us ready to go so now
这一切都为我们准备好现在就走
I'm gonna go apt and now notice that it
我会去 ，现在 注意到它
says that there are some things that can
说有些事情 可以
be upgraded so we want to do that apt
升级， 所以我们想要做到这一点
upgrade not update notice it says hey
升级不更新通知它说嘿
couldn't lock the file that's because I
无法锁定因为我而导致的文件
forgot sudo because I need to be super
忘了sudo，因为我需要 超级
user now it's gonna go through and it's
用户现在会经历，这是
gonna upgrade anything that is ready to
要 升级任何 准备好的 东西
be upgraded so are we ready to do that
提升能力，从而为我们准备这样做
yes let's do that
是的，让我们这样做
this is now downloading all of those
这是现在下载所有这些
programs off of the web and this just
关闭网络和这 只是一个程序
shows you how bare-bones my installation
向您展示 我的安装是 多么简单
of raspbian stretches here tonight
今晚 在这里 拉斯维加斯的 绵延
because there is a ton of stuff to be
因为有很多东西 需要
upgraded here I see things like like
在这里升级， 我看到 喜欢的东西
Python and even my timezone data is
Python甚至我的时区数据是
being updated so that's all happening
正在更新， 这一切都 发生了
through those repositories that's also
通过那些也是
how we're going to install plug
我们如何安装 插件
Media server tonight so let's check on
媒体服务器，今晚让我们检查
the status here it looks like it's
这里的状态看起来像是这样
working away and it can take some time
工作了，这可能需要一些时间
especially you know if you've got a
特别是你知道你是否有 一个
slower connection we're gonna use the
我们要用的连接速度较慢
magic of television to kind of speed
电视的魔力达到某种速度
this up for you tonight let's see how we
今晚给你看看我们如何
can do that okay so in real time we are
可以做到这一点，所以我们是实时的
sitting here and this has so far taken
坐在这里，这 已经采取了
about 20 minutes or so to get to this
大约20分钟左右即可完成
point in that amount of time Marsh man
指出那个时间 沼泽人 的时间
in the chat room says while this is
在聊天室里这么说
going on I downloaded and burned an SD
继续我 下载并烧毁了SD
card and booted up the new Plex PI comm
卡并启动 新的Plex PI comm
mm-hmm and now back to our post
mm-嗯，现在回到我们的 帖子
processed accelerated apt upgrade on the
处理加速apt就可以升级了
Raspberry Pi 3 and boom it's done just
树莓派3和繁荣它 刚刚 完成
like that it took no time at all
就像它没有花时间
actually it really did you're gonna have
其实它真的有你会有
to dedicate yourself some time on the
为自己奉献一些时间
Raspberry Pi 3 because it does take a
树莓派3，因为它需要一个
lot of time to update so really quickly
很多时间很快更新
now that that's been updated upgraded
现在 已更新升级
now we need to go apt dist upgrade
现在我们需要去 容易 DIST 升级
that's gonna be the next step again
那会再次成为下一步
super user do sudo apt dist upgrade and
超级用户做 sudo apt dist升级和
I'm not I'm so happy to see that it
我不是很高兴看到它
doesn't need to do any because that took
不需要做任何事情，因为这样做
a while to get through ok now we need to
现在我们需要一段时间才能完成
go sudo reboot and that's gonna restart
去sudo重启，这将重新启动
our Raspberry Pi 3 because now that
我们的树莓派3因为现在
we've got all those updates to the
我们已经得到了所有这些更新
software we need to make sure that we
我们需要确保 我们的软件
get the basically those load right they
基本上得到这些负载 他们
need to load up on the system so here we
需要加载系统，所以在这里我们
go we're rebooting into the updated
去我们重新启动到更新
raspbian stretch now if you're not
如果你不是，现在拉斯维加斯拉伸
familiar with raspbian you can head on
熟悉你可以前往的 raspbian
over to raspberry pi dot org
到树莓派 点组织
don't forget the silent P in there rasp
不要忘记锉刀中的沉默P.
berry pie dot org and as P I like the
浆果派 圆点org和像PI一样
number not I like the edible and you can
号码不是我喜欢食用，你可以
download it for free from there it's
从 那里 免费下载它
based on Debian now it tells me okay hey
现在基于Debian，它告诉我 没关系，嘿
your upgraded to the latest version
您升级 到最新 版本
congratulations thank you took long
恭喜谢谢你花了很长时间
enough ok so now next step because now
确定足够所以现在下一个 步骤 ，因为现在
that we're up to up-to-date we can
我们是不是都在跟上时代的我们 可以
finally get into installing deploying
最后进入安装部署
our plex media server now a real case
我们的Plex媒体服务器现在是一个真实的案例
for Plex PI comm comes from realizing
对于Plex PI comm来自实现
how much time the
多少时间了
can take to do this yourself right so
可以采取自己这样做的权利
we've done the work for you folks Plex
我们已经为您做了Plex的工作
Pike ami and just download it run it
派克阿米只是 下载它运行它
you're good to go so let's let's see how
你很好去，让我们来看看如何
it's done though let's actually get in
它已经完成了，让我们真正进入
there and make this happen
在那里，并做到这一点
so all right in my terminal which thank
所以在我的终端里感谢
you to the community who has let me know
你到了让 我知道的社区
hey control shift plus allows me to
嘿控制 转变加上允许我
actually zoom in on the terminal so
实际上放大 了终端
folks if you're watching at home and
如果你在家里观看和观看的话
having trouble seeing that on your
无法 看到 你的
60-inch TV well that's gonna help you
60英寸电视机，这将帮助你
out a great deal there we go so first
出了很多 ，我们继续 这样第一
thing I want to do now that we've
我们现在要做的事情就是我们现在要做的
rebooted is we need to make sure that
重新启动是我们需要确保
apt remember we did apt update and I'm
容易 记得我们做容易更新和我
tired of typing sudo so I'm gonna go
厌倦了打sudo所以我要走了
sudo su and now I am route done now
sudo su，现在我已经完成了路线
remember how when I do apt update and
请记住我什么时候做更新和
everything else that connects to the
一切连接到的东西
servers and gets its updates well we
服务器，并很好地获得它的更新
need to make sure that apt is able to
需要确保apt能够
use HTTPS SSL encrypted transport in
使用HTTPS SSL加密传输
order to do that we need to install a
为了做到这一点，我们需要安装 一个
package which may on the new stretch
可能在新的弹力包上
already be in existence but we're gonna
已经存在， 但我们会
do it anyways just to be sure it doesn't
无论如何只是为了 确保 它不会
hurt anything remember that I am now
伤害任何事情，请记住 ，我现在
route okay
路线没问题
that's what sudo su did so I don't have
这就是sudo su所做的，所以我没有
to type sudo apt install and we're gonna
键入sudo安装，我们会
just make sure apt transport HTTP hit
只要确保 传输HTTP命中
enter if you don't have it it's going to
输入，如果你没有它会去的
install it if you do it says app
安装它，如果你这样做说的应用程序
transport HTTP is already the newest
传输HTTP已经是最新的了
version so now we need to actually get
版本，所以现在我们需要真正得到
our plex media server the repository
我们的plex媒体服务器存储库
it's a PPA so we're going to add that to
这是一个PPA，所以我们将把它添加到
our system here I'm not sure if there's
我们的系统在这里 我不确定是否有
a stretch one let's give it a go so
一气一个让我们给它一个去 这样
let's go let's go over here let's do it
让我们走吧让我们一起走吧让我们 来做吧
this way
这条路
et Cie slash apt and we're gonna go into
等Cie斜削，我们会进入
sources dot list dot D and we're gonna
来源点列表点D，我们会
create a new one so I notice I'm in the
创造一个新的，所以我注意到我 在
folder etc' slash app slash sources dot
文件夹等'斜杠应用斜杠源点
list D this is where I can add all kinds
列表D这是 我可以添加各种类型的地方
of things I'm gonna call this PMS dot
我要称之为PMS点的东西
list and you can follow along with these
列表，你可以跟着 这些
this whole tutorial at cat5 dot TV slash
这整个教程在cat5点电视 斜线
PMS and to be sure it stands for plex
PMS， 并确保它代表丛
media server
媒体服务器
hmm hmm I'm creating a new file with
嗯嗯 我正在创建一个 新的文件
nano I am route so I can do this and I'm
纳米 我是 路线，所以我可以做到这一点，我是
gonna go Deb HTTP now that we've got
现在我们会去Deb HTTP
HTTP transport and we're gonna go dev
HTTP传输，我们会去开发
today dot de / PMS stretch main and then
今天dot de / PMS舒展 主力，然后
I'm going to output that with ctrl o and
我将 用 ctrl o和 输出
then ctrl X to exit app update let's see
然后按Ctrl键退出应用更新让我们来看看
if there is a stretch repository there
如果那里有拉伸库
if all goes well it's gonna it's gonna
如果一切顺利，它会去的
tell me that the key can't be found
告诉我，钥匙找不到
there we go that's good
我们去那很好
so it's found a stretch all right
所以它找到了一个舒展没事
perfect
完善
okay so the public key is not available
好吧，所以公钥 不可用
we need to get that so W get - oh do I
我们需要得到这样的结果 - 哦，我
have a pipe this time I do not okay you
这次有一个管道，我 不好意思
guys ready for this number last time on
上次为这个数字准备好了
episode number what was it for 34 59 we
剧集号码是什么34 59我们
had that trouble so let's see if I can
有这样的麻烦，让我们看看我能不能
change my keyboard settings preferences
更改我的键盘设置首选项
mouse and mouse and keyboard settings my
鼠标和 鼠标和 键盘设置 我的
mouse is very sluggish by the way so
这样鼠标非常迟钝
that's why I'm moving in slow motion
这就是我为什么要慢动作的原因
here keyboard keyboard layout Raspberry
这里键盘键盘布局覆盆子
Pi being based in the UK they've
Pi 在英国工作
defaulted this to a UK keyboard now I
现在我默认这是英国键盘
want to change to a United States
想改变为美国
keyboard you may need to change to
您可能需要更改键盘
something that's more appropriate to you
更适合你的东西
and I'm gonna choose English your yes
我会选择英语 你的是
now I'm gonna have that pipe character
现在我要拥有那个管角色了
unlike last time okay and then okay Wow
不像上次没关系， 然后好的哇
is that every sluggish Wow
是每个呆滞的哇
okay do I have pipe yes okay W get -
好吧我有管道是 好的 W得到 -
capital o that is the letter O and then
大写字母o就是字母O然后
- yes that's intentional we're gonna
- 是的， 我们会 故意的
output this and import it into the next
输出这个并导入到下一个
command HTTP colon slash slash dev - de
命令HTTP结肠斜线斜杠dev  -  de
de / PMS slash dev - de -
de / PMS斜线dev  -  de  -
PMS gpg key don't worry you can copy and
PMS的gpg密钥 不用担心你可以复制和
paste that at cat 5 TV / PMS and then
粘贴 在猫5电视 / PMS然后
pipe and then sudo apt - key add - so
管道，然后sudo apt  -  key add  -  so
what we're saying is grab that key and
我们所说的是抓住那把钥匙， 并且
output it to - we'll say from dev today
输出它- 我们今天会从开发者那里说
doc de /p
doc de / p
GPG chi blah blah blah then pipe it into
然后把它插入到 GPG chi等等等等等等
sudo apt key ad - that's gonna download
关键广告 - 这是 要下载
and import the key all in one fell swoop
并一举将密钥导入
without actually putting the file on my
而没有真正将文件放在我的
hard drive now if I go apt update if all
现在硬盘驱动器， 如果 我去 更新，如果全部
went well
顺利
we will not see those error messages
我们不会看到这些错误消息
this time because the private the public
这次是因为私人大众
key is now available right and it worked
关键是现在可用的权利，它的工作
ok so now we're ready to install plex
确定，所以现在我们已经准备好 要 安装的plex
media server this is where things have
媒体服务器， 这是 事情的 地方
changed a little bit in Debian stretch
在Debian中稍微改变了一点
or in raspy and stretch in our case the
或在我们的情况下，在饶舌 和舒展
package name has changed so we're gonna
包名称已更改， 所以我们会去的
go aft install plex media server
去aft 安装Plex媒体服务器
- installer ok now before I hit enter on
- 安装程序确定 之前， 我打开输入
that I'm going to bring up my browser
我要去把 我的浏览器
here so that you can just see what is
在这里，以便您可以看到是什么
going to be different and you can see
会有所不同， 你可以看到
that a little bit of sluggishness to the
那一点点迟钝了
Raspberry Pi 3 that's what I was talking
树莓派3这就是我 所说的
about when when we were talking last
关于何时我们最后说话的时间
week about how performance feels more
周关于表现如何感觉更多
like a desktop on the Xu for Q if I go
如果我去的话，就像在 徐的台式机上一样
HTTP colon slash slash localhost colon
HTTP冒号斜杠斜杠localhost冒号
32400 slash web it's going to tell me
32400 斜杠web它会告诉我
that such a thing does not exist ok
这样的事情不存在 好
that's where Plex is going to live in
这就是Plex将要生活的地方
just a couple of moments time I'm going
只是一对夫妇 的 时刻，时间我要去
to hit enter and it's found it it's
打进入，它发现它
installing it fantastic
安装它太棒了
so again repositories save the day makes
如此反复存储库保存一天 品牌
it super super easy and it's grabbing a
它超级超级简单 ，它 抓住了一个
couple of extra packages that are needed
几个额外的包是需要的
that's fantastic
那太棒了
while we wait for that you know what
而我们等着你知道什么
this is not even taking very long this
这甚至不需要很长时间
mom this is motoring along I'm gonna
妈妈， 这是驾驶沿着我要去
bring up another terminal window and
打开另一个终端窗口，
we're gonna zoom in on that one and
我们会放大那一个和
we're gonna go sudo su and I gotta get
我们要去sudo su，我必须得到
started with the next step while I'm
从 我下一步 开始
waiting so I'm gonna go nano
等待，所以我要去纳米
slash et Cie default and plex media
slash和Cie默认和plex媒体
server which the file already exists
该文件已存在的服务器
because it's halfway done installing so
因为安装 过程已经 完成了一半
this is my configuration file and I need
这是我的配置文件 ，我需要
to tell it what user to run as you see
告诉它看到什么用户运行
how plex media server user is currently
Plex媒体服务器用户当前的状态
set to Plex well on the Raspberry Pi the
在 Raspberry Pi 上设置好Plex
user is called pi so output that with
用户被称为pi，因此输出
control o and then control X now that is
控制o然后控制X现在就是
ready for us so it's going to be running
为我们做好准备，所以它会继续 运行
as that I also need to change the
因为我也需要改变
ownership of that file just so that
该文件的所有权只是 为了
we've got access to its CH own not the
我们有权 访问 它自己的CH，而不是
file pardon me but the the folder which
文件原谅我，但该文件夹，其
is going to contain plex media server
将 包含Plex媒体服务器
but I need to wait until this process is
但我需要等到 这个 过程
done because it's still adding some
因为它还在增加一些
files but I can get ready for it CH own
文件，但我可以 为 它自己 做好准备
- R which means recursive pi PI so
-  R这意味着递归pi PI所以
that's the PI user and the PI group
那就是PI用户和PI组
because that's who we're gonna be
因为那就是我们将要成为的人
running as VAR Lib plex media server so
像VAR Lib Plex媒体服务器 那样运行
I gotta wait for this to finish before I
我必须等到这 之前 完成
hit enter because they're still gonna be
打进入， 因为他们仍然 会
some files that are gonna be dropped
一些文件将被丢弃
into that folder and then we'll be good
进入该文件夹，然后我们会很好
to go
去
once again feels like I want to speed
再次感觉我想加快速度
this up for you it's moving along
这对你来说是一个动态的过程
anyways a little better than the last
反正比上一点好一点
one but it is not an exciting process to
一个，但它不是一个令人兴奋的过程
sit there watching it you'll feel so
坐在那里看你会感觉如此
much better just to boot up flex PI I
更好地启动灵活的 PI I
guarantee it but there's a certain
保证它，但有一定的
thrill that comes from doing it yourself
来自 自己 做的快感
isn't there and you can really customize
不在那里，你可以真正定制
it now that that's ready let's zoom in
现在已经 准备好让我们放大
again so I'm going CH own recursively
所以我要递归地去CH
we're gonna go pi pi which means pi : pi
我们要去pi pi这意味着 pi：pi
PI user PI group that folder so now that
现在， PI用户 PI组该文件夹
folder belongs to
文件夹属于
so it's ready so now system CTL restart
所以现在就准备好了，现在系统CTL重新启动
plex media server because we've changed
Plex媒体服务器，因为我们已经改变
the user that we want it to run as so we
我们希望它运行 的 用户
need to restart it
需要重新启动它
system CTL status plex media server and
系统CTL状态plex媒体服务器和
we see that it is active running well it
我们看到它是积极的 运行以及它
could this be true let's go back to our
这可能是真的让我们回到我们的
web browser and we're gonna hit f5 on
网页浏览器 ，我们会打f5
the page that says cannot be reached and
说 不能到达的页面和
ladies and gentlemen we now have plex on
女士们，先生们 ，我们现在有 对 丛
our Raspberry Pi 3 amazing quite a bit
我们的Raspberry Pi 3令人惊讶不少
more onerous than just downloading Plex
比下载 Plex 更麻烦
PI comm and installing it on a flash
PI 通信并将其安装 在闪存上
drive and getting up and running but as
驾驶，起床和跑步， 但如
I say such a victorious feeling to do it
我说这样一个胜利的感觉去做
yourself ok learn along the way you
你自己好，一路学习 你
could go to the store and buy lasagne or
可以去商店购买 千层面或
you could make a lasagna at home I'm not
你可以在家做一个烤宽面条我不是
even gonna talk about the robot grandma
甚至会谈论机器人奶奶
who could make that lasagna for you and
谁可以 为你 做 这个烤宽面条
it would eat just like grandma used to
它会 像以前的奶奶一样 吃东西
make there it is folks that is Plex on
使那里的人们是Plex的 上
the Raspberry Pi three two different
Raspberry Pi 三个不同
ways to do it DIY or just download it
如何 做DIY或只是下载 它
and go check out more you can get your
并去看看更多，你 可以得到你的
pie at cat5 TV slash pie that's the
馅饼在猫5电视斜线派 这是
device that you need nice and cheap nice
设备，你需要漂亮和便宜的好
little piece of hardware that comes like
小的硬件 自带 像
that get yourself a power supply for it
这让自己为 它 的电源
an SD card something that has a
一个SD卡的东西，有一个
reasonable amount of space say 32 gigs
合理数量的空间说32演出
or so to get up and going then you're
或者这样起床和去那么你
gonna use usb with an external hard
要用 外部硬盘来 使用usb
drive or an ass share or something like
驾驶或 驴共享或 类似的东西
that in order to store your media we're
为了存储 您的媒体 我们
gonna look at how Plex actually
我们来看看Plex 究竟如何
functions next week we're going to take
我们将在下周举行活动
it from here and show you how to use it
它从这里展示如何使用它
so that's Plex on the Raspberry Pi find
所以这是树莓派发现的Plex
out more cat5 dot TV slash p-m ass we've
我们有更多的cat5 dot电视剧
got to take a really quick break when we
当我们需要一个非常快速的休息时间
come back we're gonna be we've got a
回来我们会是 我们 有一个
prize to give away that's right we've
奖励给予 我们的权利
got a winner of our video game giveaway
获得了我们的视频游戏赠品的优胜者
and the news room
和新闻室
[Music]
[音乐]
now here's another great way you can
现在这里的另一个伟大的方式 ，你 可以
support the shows you love for the
支持你 的 爱表演
category five dot TV network by shopping
五类 网点电视网购物
gearbest that's right Jeff cap five dot
gearbest 这是正确的杰夫帽五点
TV slash gearbest
电视剧斜杠 gearbest
it's an online store for the geek streak
这是一个极客连胜的网上商店
in you or the loved ones of course I
在你或我的亲人当然
mean especially your loved ones right
特别是指你的亲人
because cap 5 TV slash gearbest quite
因为第 5章 电视机 很 厉害
frankly has all of the greatest tech
坦率地说，拥有所有最伟大的技术
gifts that you can ever hope for at
你可以 期待的礼物
rock-bottom prices
最低价格
did that cellphones you betcha cap 5 TV
你打了 5台电视机 吗？
slash gear best has a wide assortment of
最好的 减速齿轮 有各式各样的
unlocked Android cell phones and tablets
解锁Android手机和平板电脑
what about computer
电脑怎么样？
consumer electronics those make a great
这些消费电子产品非常棒
gift absolutely from high tech watches
绝对来自高科技手表的礼物
to action cameras headphones even
甚至可以动作相机耳机
virtual reality headsets cat5 dot TV
虚拟现实耳机cat5点电视
slash gearbest has you covered they
斜杠gearbest你有没有覆盖 他们
literally have it all Jeff literally
从字面上将所有杰夫从字面上理解
really it's like a superstore right from
真的，它就像是一个 超市
the comfort of your own chair at your
在你自己的椅子上舒适
computer through the interweb yeah
电脑通过 interweb是啊
I there's no way they have it all it's
我不可能拥有 这一切
true that's just a bunch of random
真的，这只是一堆随机
electronic sesame what about clothes yep
电子 芝麻衣服是什么
both men and women fashionable apparel
无论男女时尚服装
at rock-bottom
在底部
SuperDuper prices kind of like this well
SuperDuper价格有点像这样
look at this coat what do you think it's
看看这件大衣你觉得这是什么
a slimming mock leather jacket it's
一个纤细的模拟皮夹克
available for less than $30 plus free
可用于少于30美元加免费
shipping at camp five TV slash gear best
最好 在 营地的 五台 电视机上运送
yeah all right it kind of got me there
是的，所有这一切都 让 我在那里
Wow any other questions for me Jeff now
哇， 现在 给我杰夫任何其他问题
that the winter is past flying season do
，冬季是飞过去的季节 做
they have any good deals on say copters
他们在 说直升机方面有很多优惠
oh my goodness well check this out dude
哦，我的天啊， 好好检查一下这 家伙
they have everything check out over 500
他们有一切检查 超过500
various drums and not only that they're
各种各样的鼓 ，而不仅仅是他们
available marked down by about 32 up to
可用降低了 大约32 到
63 percent off the regular price love it
普通价格的 63％ 喜欢它
what's the website again well you're
你的网站 又是什么？
gonna find gearbest on our partners
会在我们的合作伙伴身上 找到 gearbest
pages for any of your favorite category
任何你喜欢的类别的页面
5 TV shows like new every day
5个电视节目每天都像新的一样
category 5 technology TV the pixel
5类技术电视像素
shadow but of course if you want to shop
影子， 但 当然，如果你想购物
absolutely right now and you want to go
绝对是现在，你想去
straight to the site all you have to do
直接到 网站所有你需要做的
is visit cat5 dot TV slash gearbest see
正在访问cat5点 电视剧大减速器 见
that's easy tech 5 dot TV slash gearbest
这很容易高科技5点电视斜线 gearbest
that's right
那就对了
happy shopping welcome back this is
欢迎购物，欢迎回来
category 5 technology TV so nice to have
第5类技术电视真好
you here check out our website category
你在这里查看 我们的网站类别
5 dot TV lots of great ways to
5点电视很多伟大的方式来
participate such as as winning a copy of
参加比如 赢得副本
that effects VR that effect to VR yes we
那影响VR对VR的影响是的，我们
have been having a contest and we pick a
一直在进行比赛，我们选择一个
winner each week now the way to enter
每周赢家都是现在进入的方式
the contest is to let us know how you're
比赛是让我们知道你是怎么样的
watching where you're watching from you
看你在哪里看你
do that by email email contest at
通过邮件电子邮件比赛在那里做
category 5 dot TV easy pv it's too easy
类别 5 点电视容易 光伏它太容易了
to win folks we've counted up this week
赢得本周我们已经计算好的人
not hundreds not thousands but several
不是数百而不是成千上万，但几个
of your ballots
的选票
and this week this week's winner is Sam
本周的获胜者是山姆
okay lickin one kiss listen x11 what's
好吧 lickin一个吻x11是什么
your next one way to go congratulations
你的下一个路去祝贺
you are our winner this week all of
你本周 是我们的 赢家
these dead effects to VR players are
这些对VR玩家的 死效果 是
gonna just seat somewhere get steamed
只要坐在某个地方蒸就可以了
set up get her going we'll send you the
设置让她去，我们会送你
passcode to download that right after
密码下载后 右
the show
演出
congratulations here are the stories
祝贺这里是故事
were covering this week in the category
这个星期在这个类别中
5 TV newsroom an IT worker who
5电视 新闻室是一名IT工作者
accidentally threw out a hard drive
不小心抛出了硬盘
containing a small cache of Bitcoin has
包含比特币的小缓存
lost over 100 million dollars because of
失去了100多万美元， 因为
the blender investigations have been
搅拌器的调查已经 完成
launched after a helicopter reportedly
据报道，在一架直升机后发射
crashed when swerving to avoid a
转弯时避免碰撞时坠毁
consumer drone a Japanese company is
消费者无人机是一家日本公司
planning to build the world's tallest
筹建世界最高
wooden skyscraper in 2041
2041年的木制摩天大楼
to mark its three hundred and fiftieth
以纪念其三百 五十分之一
anniversary a mountain of sensitive
周年纪念敏感的山
FedEx consumer data has been exposed and
联邦快递的消费数据已经暴露和
Microsoft has back ported its Windows
微软已经移植了它的Windows
Defender advanced threat protection
后卫高级威胁保护
security toolkit from Windows 10 to
从Windows 10到安全工具包
Windows 7 and 8.1 these stories are
Windows 7 和8.1 这些故事都是
coming right up
马上就来
don't go anywhere whether you shop on
不管你是否购物，都不要去任何地方
ThinkGeek gearbest B&amp;H Photo Video eBay
ThinkGeek gearbest B＆H照片视频eBay
or Amazon or even if you want a free
或亚马逊，或者即使你想免费
trial of audible you'll find the best
听到审判你会发现最好的
deals and support the shows we produce
交易和支持我们制作的节目
by simply visiting the shopping sites
通过访问购物网站
you already frequent by using the links
你已经经常使用链接
on our website visit category-five TV
在我们的网站上访问 五类电视
slash partners for the full and
为全面斜线合作伙伴和
ever-growing list and help us create
不断增长的名单， 并帮助我们创造
more free content like this show thank
像这样的 更多免费 内容显示谢谢
you for shopping with our partners and
你和我们的合作伙伴一起购物
thank you for watching
感谢您的 收看
this is the category 5 TV newsroom
这是第 5 类 电视 新闻编辑室
covering the week's top tech stories
涵盖本周的顶级技术故事
with a slight Linux - I'm Sasha Rickman
轻微的 Linux  - 我是Sasha Rickman
and here the top stories were following
这里的最重要的故事在继续
this week an IT worker who accidentally
本周一名IT员工无意中
threw out a hard drive containing a
扔出一个包含a的硬盘
small cache of Bitcoin has so far lost
迄今为止，比特币的小缓存已经丢失
over 100 million dollars because of the
超过1亿美元， 因为
blunder we've reported on this a number
大错， 我们已经报道了这个 数字
of years ago as well but as Bitcoin
年前还有而是作为比特币
continues to grow the time has come to
不断增长的时间已经到来
revisit this the story dates back to
重温这个故事可以追溯到
2013 when James Howells had who had been
2013当詹姆斯·豪厄尔斯已经谁 曾
mining cryptocurrency on his computer
在他的电脑上挖掘cryptocurrency
since 2009 to solve complex mathematical
自2009年起解决复杂的数学问题
problems and earn rewards dismantled the
问题和赚取奖励 拆除了
device after spilling a drink on it he
装置后，他喝了一杯饮料
said after I had stopped mining the
在我停止采矿之后说
laptop I had used was broken into parts
我曾经使用的笔记本电脑被分解成部分
and sold on eBay however I kept the hard
并在eBay上出售，但我保持艰难
drive in a drawer at home knowing it
在家里的抽屉里开车知道
contained my Bitcoin private keys so
包含我的比特币私钥
that if Bitcoin did become valuable one
如果比特币 确实变得有价值的话
day I would still have the coins I had
那天我仍然会有我拥有的硬币
mined he continued in mid 2013 during a
开采过程中 ，他在 2013年中期 继续
clear outs the hard drive then worth a
清除硬盘驱动器，然后值得一个
few hundred thousand pounds was
几十万英镑是
mistakenly thrown out and put into a
错误地抛出并投入了
general waste bin at my local landfill
一般垃圾箱 在我当地的垃圾填埋场
site after which it was buried on site
之后它被埋在现场
the hard drive contains 7500 bitcoins at
硬盘上包含7500比特币
that time that amount of Bitcoin was
那个时候那个比特币的数量是多少
worth about 700 thousand dollars but
但价值约 70万美元
Bitcoin didn't stop there had he had not
比特币并没有停止曾有 他没有
thrown away that drive it would have
扔掉 驱动 它会对
amounted to over 100 million dollars 119
总额超过1亿美元119
million five hundred and one thousand
百万 五千一千
nine hundred and twenty-five dollars you
你九百二十五美元
asked as of last week while Howells had
问上周的 同时豪厄尔斯有
made several requests to the local
向当地人提出了几个要求
council to dig up and salvage the hard
理事会挖掘并 挽救困难
drive at this site he has yet to be
在这个地方驾驶他还没有
granted permission to look for the
授予 许可 查找
missing treasure he says I haven't
失踪的宝藏，他说我没有
actually tried to search for the hard
实际上试图寻找困难
drive yet as I have not been given
因为我没有得到
permission to look despite having
尽管拥有许可权
financial backing in place and engaging
财务支持到位和参与
the local council a couple of times
当地议会几次
Howells who calls himself a Bitcoin
豪威尔斯 自称比特币
pioneer and Bitcoin cache proponent on
先锋和比特币 缓存支持者
Twitter says that he will not give up on
Twitter表示他不会放弃
his search on December 2nd 2017 he
他在2017年12月2日搜索他
tweeted a diagram
啾啾图
of a modern landfill with the
一个现代化的垃圾填埋场 用的
bittersweet caption Bitcoin cold storage
bittersweet标题比特币冷库
vaults I remember this story I recall
拱顶我记得这个故事， 我记得
you doing this story years back it makes
你做这个故事多年后，它使
me so sad for this guy and I every time
我每次都 为这个 人和我感到悲伤
Bitcoin goes up a coin is constantly
比特币不断上涨
going up and has been going up but good
上升，并 一直在 上涨，但很好
news is that he tweeted on December 7th
消息是他在12月 7 日发布了推文
seems to be in good spirits has not
似乎精神状态并不好
taken his own life so this is this is
采取他自己的生活，所以 这是这样的
Grace on the up-and-up I cannot believe
我无法 相信 恩典的上下
he's waiting for permission like I feel
他正在等待我的感觉
like if this was me with a hundred
如果这是我的一百
million dollars I might be sneaking in
我可能会偷偷摸摸地进来
under the cover of darkness and when
在黑暗 和何时 的掩护下
you're telling a story again I can't
你又讲一个 故事， 我不能
help but think about Shizue Yamaguchi
帮助，但想想Shizue山口
coming on the show and talking to us
出席演出并与 我们 交谈
about decluttering yeah I cleaning up
关于垃圾 是我 清理
cleaning house the Mary Kondo method and
打扫房子玛丽Kondo方法和
I might be wrong in my recall on this
我对此的回忆可能是 错误的
but I do not believe it was him who
但我不相信他是谁
threw it out was it the people from
把它扔出去是它的人民
hoarders that came in and like took all
进来和喜欢的囤积者夺走了所有
this stuff and threw that something
这东西 ，扔了东西
makes me think it was his wife and I
让我觉得这是他和我的妻子
don't know whether it's because I'm a
不知道是不是因为 我是
wife but I just imagine that's the kind
妻子， 但我只是想象那是种
of thing that a wife would do I guess
我估计妻子会做的事情
believe me it's true how many times have
相信我有多少次是真的
I been like where is such and such tech
我一直喜欢在哪里这样和那样的 技术
device and then I find it
设备，然后我找到它
years later in the bottom of a box
几年后，在一个盒子的底部
because there's a box that says random
因为有一个 随机 的框
miscellaneous rabi things exactly at
杂项rabi的东西 正好 在
least they don't go to the dump
至少他们不去倾倒
oops okay so I want to know okay how
哎呀好吧，所以我想 知道 如何
like would that usually be okay if you
如果 你愿意，通常会很好
took a hard drive out could you just put
你可以放下硬盘
it in a safe and yours leader would it
它在一个安全的和你的领导者会
be okay if it had Bitcoin on it like is
如果 它上面有比特币就可以
that obvious I wouldn't trust it right
那显然我不会相信它是正确的
certainly it's certainly not yes and no
当然， 这肯定不是，也不是
I mean cuz so many things could happen
我的意思是，很多事情都可能发生
putting a drive in a drawer right
把一个驱动器抽屉 权
sensitive to electrostatic sensitive to
对静电敏感
vibration as people open and close the
振动就像人们打开和关闭的一样
drawer sensitive to people coming in and
抽屉敏感的人进来 和
throwing out the things that are in the
抛出这 是美国的 事情
drawer granted he did spill a drink on
抽屉给他喝了一杯
it to begin with so he's not exactly
它开始，所以他不 完全
up-and-up on the safe keeping of his
向上和向上上 的安全保存 他的
Bitcoin yeah
比特币是的
yeah okay so if we're gonna mine
好吧，好吧，如果我们要开采
cryptocurrency first of all yeah you're
加密货币首先是你是
gonna get a string of words or a
会得到一串文字或一串
decryption key a private key they this
解密密钥他们这个私钥
is what it was stored on that hard drive
是它 存储在 该 硬盘上的
the Bitcoin itself is not stored on the
比特币本身不存储在
hard drive
硬盘
the Bitcoin is in the Internet it's like
比特币就像互联网一样
just they call it the the the blockchain
只是他们称之为 区块链
it's in this blockchain so many many
它在这个区块链中有很多很多
computers have that Bitcoin coded into
计算机将比特币编码为
them but in order to access those
他们，但为了访问这些
Bitcoin you have to have the private key
比特币你必须拥有私钥
so their Bitcoin out there that people
所以他们的比特币就在那里
can see that it's not tangible but
可以看到它不是有形的， 但是
numbers it's it's digital binary stuff
数字它是数字二进制的东西
with with the decryption key though or
与解密密钥虽然或
with the part of me the private key you
与我的部分私钥你
can access that as money I kind of
可以像我这种钱一样存取
myself right
我自己 对
so had he had multiple copies of that
所以他有多个副本
key or had he printed that key and put
钥匙或他打印了该钥匙并放好
it in the filing capsule so this could
它在归档胶囊中， 所以这可以
easily be just to back up your stuff oh
很容易只是为了备份 你的东西哦
my gosh right especially if you have
我的天哪，尤其是如果你有
7500 Bitcoin at the time even when they
即使在他们的时候也是 7500比特币
were $1 each that's $7,500 and at the
分别是 $ 1,500美元和 1 美元
time when he had this discarded it was
当他丢弃它的时候是
$700,000 I cannot believe he's so I like
700,000美元我不敢相信他是如此我喜欢
Jessica he thinks he's gonna find this
杰西卡， 他认为他会找到这个
you're not fine in it no well at this
你不好在这
point it's been so many years buried in
它已经 埋葬了很多年了
the muck
泥土
when you buried in the muck what do they
当你埋在泥土里时他们是什么
do at landfills they put things on top
他们在垃圾填埋场里把东西放在最前面
of it and they put chemicals and yeah
它和他们把化学品和是啊
types of bacteria that eat away at the
在食物上消灭的细菌类型
things that are buried there right okay
事情埋葬在那里 的权利 好吗
so when it was in your drawer was
所以当它在你的抽屉里
already possibly subject to some it
已经可能受到一些影响
should had some 7up all over it yeah and
应该有一些7up全部是耶和
now it's a know you're never sorry buddy
现在，这是一个知道你从来没有抱歉的 好友
if you're gonna mine cryptocurrency once
如果你要去挖一次cryptocurrency
you get up to
你起床了
a half a Bitcoin you got to know it's
一半的比特币 你就知道了
time to like backup your backups put it
时间喜欢 备份 你的备份
in a safety deposit box print it print
在保险箱内打印
it when the electromagnetic pulse comes
当电磁 脉冲来临时
from the alien invaders you have to have
从外来入侵者你必须拥有
a paper copy I will say I hope this guy
一份纸本我会说我希望这个人
is still happily married but if he's not
仍然幸福地结婚，但如果他不是
he should never say on his first date
他不应该 在他的第一次约会上 说
that he does not a way to introduce
他 没有办法介绍
yourself I could be out of McDonald's
我自己可以 走出 麦当劳
right now I have a story for why this is
现在 我有一个故事，为什么这是
our first date I would be wining and
我们的第一次约会， 我会赢
dining you downtown not a good pick-up
在市中心用餐并不是一个好的 选择
line investigations have been launched
行调查已经展开
after a helicopter reportedly crashed
据报道，一架直升机坠毁
while swerving to avoid a consumer drone
同时避免消费无人机
a trainee had been practicing hovering
一名学员一直在练习徘徊
about 50 feet above trees on Daniel
大约在丹尼尔树上 50英尺 处
Island South Carolina seeing a
南卡罗来纳州 看到了
quadcopter flying towards them the
quadcopter飞向他们
instructor took control but clipped a
教练取得了控制权，但却裁掉了一名
tree with the tail rotor router causing
树尾部转子 路由器造成的
the helicopter to crash to the ground
直升机坠毁到地面
and tip onto its side the drone is
和尖端到其一侧的无人驾驶飞机
believed to have been a DJI phantom DJI
相信已经有DJI幻影DJI
says that they are trying to learn more
说他们正在努力学习更多
about this incident and stand ready to
关于这起事件， 并准备好了
assist investigators they also added
他们还协助调查人员补充说
that they do provide owners with help to
他们确实为 业主提供帮助
ensure that they steer clear of
确保他们避开
traditional aircraft industry groups
传统飞机制造业 集团
representing large US airlines pilots
代表美国大型航空公司 飞行员
and air traffic controllers have
和空中交通管制员有
previously urged the US Federal Aviation
此前敦促美国联邦航空
Administration which has also launched
也启动了管理
an investigation into the crash to end
对撞车事件的调查结束
exemptions that currently prevents it
目前阻止它的豁免
from regulating consumer drones a letter
从管理消费者无人机的信件
co-signed by three organizations warns
三个组织共同签署警告
the likelihood that a drone will collide
无人机将发生碰撞的可能性
with an aircraft airline aircraft is
与飞机的航空公司 是
increasing it is increasing because
越来越多，因为
there's more drones out there yeah and
有更多的无人机是耶和华
it's scary I hope that the pilot and the
这是可怕的， 我希望飞行员和
student are okay now there was no
学生都还好 现在没有
mention of that I think I think that
何况， 我认为 我认为，
they must be okay and that it would be a
他们必须 是 可以的， 这将是一个
much bigger story if they were not oh
如果他们不是哦，那么更大的故事
sure yeah you know what you're right
当然， 你知道你说得对
absolutely if they were hurt or right
绝对 如果他们受伤或是 对的
worse it would be bigger news but even
更糟的是，这将是更大的消息，但甚至
if there are what I mean
如果有我的意思
I'm certain that there are some amounts
我确信有 一些金额
of pain if you're 50 feet above the
如果你的 身高 超过 50英尺 就会感到疼痛
treeline and you fall but okay I'm
treeline和你跌倒但 没关系，我是
assuming that they're alive and even if
假设 他们还活着 ，即使如此
they okay who pays for this is where
他们没关系，谁支付这是在哪里
this is going no how you segue to that
这是怎么回事，不，你如何Segue公司于
okay so these people are on the ground
好吧，这些人 在地上
and there is their obviously hurt in
并且在 他们中有明显的 伤害
some way and they have to go to the hole
某种方式，他们 必须去洞
they just lost my helicopter that's got
他们刚刚失去了我的直升机 那种 有
to be worth a couple of Bitcoin right so
这样才 值得 几个 比特币
the drone flier is clearly at fault
无人驾驶飞行器显然 是错误的
right because I would in this I mean I'm
对，因为我会在这我的意思是我
not the judge and jury on this one but
而不是法官和 陪审团在这一个，但
the drone was flying around we don't
无人机飞来飞去，我们没有
have any inkling as to how close they
有任何暗示， 他们有多接近
were but it was the pilots error that
但是这是飞行员的错误
hit the tree that's what took down the
击中了那个击倒了那棵树的树
helicopter now had that drone gotten
直升机现在已经得到了无人机
close you know what's happening
关闭你知道发生了什么
if it got on top of those rotors done
如果它完成 了这些转子的顶部
sucked down and shattered and who knows
吸了下来，破碎了，谁知道
what kind of mess right could have been
什么样的混乱权可能是
worse it could have been worse I still I
更糟的是， 它可能会 更糟， 我仍然是我
okay they were 50 feet they hit a tree
好吧，他们是50英尺他们击中了一棵树
that's what took them down so they were
这就是让他们失望的原因
20 feet they hit at that point right the
他们打在这一点上20英尺权
hit a tree to avoid a drone that was
撞上了一棵树，以避免无人驾驶飞机 ，这 是
perhaps coming toward that me in my mind
也许是 在我的脑海里 向 我诉说
it's like barreling toward them at the
这就像在他们身上向他们滚滚而来
feet of the way matrix-style
英尺矩阵式的脚
okay so they panicked they panicked yeah
好吧，所以他们惊慌失措，他们惊慌失措
so is there insurance did DJ DJ I but
那么DJ DJ I还有保险 吗？
the the pilot instructor would have had
这位飞行员 教练本来 会有的
insurance of course on the craft itself
保险当然是关于工艺本身的
right so they'd be covered now how do
正确的， 所以他们会被覆盖 现在怎么做
you track down the pilot of the drone
你追踪无人机的飞行员
good luck there now if DJI is helping
如果DJI帮助，现在好运
they may have GPS data but they have
他们可能有GPS数据，但他们有
been under a lot of heat for holding on
一直在忍受着 很大的热度
to GPS data so guess what they're
以GPS数据，所以猜猜他们是什么
apparently not doing that anymore or
显然不再那样做或
they're hiding the fact that they're
他们隐藏了他们的事实
doing that so who really knows it does
这样做， 所以谁真正 知道它
say DJI helps drone fliers avoid a
DJI帮助无人驾驶飞行器避免了一个
medication for education so like when
用于教育的药物如此喜欢
you see a plane oh and through the
你看到一架飞机哦，通过
feature
特征
right they will you can't fly your drone
他们会让你无法驾驶你的无人机
into a no-fly zone if you are a good
进入禁飞区，如果你是个好人
pilot if you're a good player a good
飞行员如果你是一个优秀的球员 一个很好的
player does not disable their GPS in
球员不禁止其 在 GPS
there and the geofencing right
那里和geofencing权利
geofencing will stop your drone dead
地理围栏将阻止你的无人机死亡
stop if you are approaching a no-fly
如果你正在接近 禁飞， 就停下来
zone
区
some people will turn off that feature
有些人会关闭该功能
on their drone I just hadn't want to
在他们的无人机上， 我只是 不想
keep a lightbulb moment yeah
保持 灯泡的 时刻 是啊
can each commercial aircraft each
每个商业飞机都可以
helicopter and plane can they not have
直升机和飞机是他们没有的
like a beacon of some sort that does
就像某种类型的灯塔一样
like a force field I think I know where
像一个力场， 我 想我知道在哪里
you're going with you like here's my
你和 你一样喜欢这里是我的
theory protective bubble it's probably
理论保护泡沫 可能
not a good idea on an aircraft to have a
不是飞机上的 好主意 ，有一个
transmitter that takes down aircraft
发射器， 它 记下飞机
right I see what you're saying yes but
好吧， 我明白 你说的没错，但
if it was a signal if it was a like a
如果这是一个信号，如果它是一个像
radio signal the broadcasts 50 yards in
无线电信号播出50码
front and around right then and and the
前面和 右边然后和和
drone had a feature to receive that and
无人机有一个功能来接收和
say oh I'm getting too close but these
说哦，我越来越近，但这些
are things that are traveling at super
是超级 旅行的东西
speeds I'm picturing like Star Trek or
速度我像星际迷航 或
Star Wars whichever it is that is in the
星球大战，无论它是在哪里
Stars has the force field that goes
星星有力量场
around Star Trek has right collector
周围的星际迷航有权利收集
dishes and force fields right so okay
菜肴和武力领域，所以没关系
ken planes not have that in theory but
肯恩 飞机理论上不具备这一点
for just base like it did welcome to
只为 基地喜欢 它欢迎
reality Sasha I'd love to be able to say
萨沙我很乐意能够说出的现实
the Star Trek is real but alas no but
星际迷航是真实的，但唉，但是
it's science fiction like just something
它就像科幻小说 一样
that pulses they're working like okay
该脉冲他们正在像 没事
they're working on it also
他们正在努力也
faster-than-light Drive they're working
他们正在努力的比他们更快的光驱
on it not yet a thing idea right my idea
在它上面还没有一个想法正确的想法
is this is the how drones like the way
这是怎么样的 无人驾驶飞机 喜欢的方式
you think yeah this is how a force field
你认为耶 这 是 一个 怎样 的 力场
and faster-than-light Drive dilithium I
并且比光速更快驱动二锂 I
don't know it started somewhere
不知道它开始在某个地方
a Japanese company is planning to build
一家日本公司正在计划建设
the world's tallest wooden skyscraper in
世界上最高的木制摩天大楼
2041 to markets three hundred and
2041年到市场三百
fiftieth anniversary summit tomo
五十周年峰会tomo
forestry said ten percent of the 70
林业部门表示，70％的人中有10％
story w 350 tower would be steel
故事瓦350塔将是钢铁
combined with about one hundred and
加上约一百个
eighty thousand cubic meters of
80000立方米 的
indigenous wood enough to build about
土著木材足以建立约
eight thousand homes with trees and
八千个树木 和 家园
foliage on balconies at every level it
对每阳台枝叶它级
said a braced tube structure diagonal
说支撑管 结构 对角线
diagonal steel vibration controlled
对角钢振动控制
braces at the center of a three hundred
大括号在三百人的中心
and fifty meter wood and steel column
和 五十米的木材和钢柱
would protect against Tokyo's regular
将保护东京的正常
earthquakes the projected cost of the
地震的预计成本
building is about six hundred billion
建筑 约有六百 十亿
yen more than five and a half billion US
日元超过五十五亿美元
dollars which is about twice the cost of
这大约是美元成本的 两倍
a conventional skyscraper of the same
相同的传统摩天大楼
size but Sumitomo said that it's
大小，但住友说，这是
expected that the costs will fall before
预计 成本将下降前
completion due to technological
由于技术完成
breakthroughs a block of student flats
突破一批 学生单位
in Vancouver was currently the world's
在温哥华当前是全球的
tallest wooden skyscraper at 53 meters
最高的木制摩天大楼，高53 米
so this is about three hundred meters
所以这是 关于300米
taller than the current world holder the
比现在的世界持有者高
300 the W 350 tower would be used for
300的W 350 塔将用于
offices shops hotels and homes I love
办公室商店我爱的酒店和家园
stuff that would be stunning are you
那些令人惊叹的东西就是你
imagine so if it's happening in that
想象一下，如果它发生在那
many years right 2040 G they got a lot
2040年的许多年， 他们获得了很多
of time to prepare and save up like they
的时间来 准备和保存起来 像他们
could probably plant the trees that are
很可能的植物， 是树
going to be used the would probably have
将被使用的可能会
deflectors by then I know right okay
然后我知道对方好吧
well so bang on with that that girl she
好吧，那么 那个女孩就 这么激动
knows it all yeah right how how is a
知道这一切 是啊，怎么是一个
braced tube structure gonna protect a
支撑管结构会保护一个
wooden structure from earthquakes you
来自地震的木结构你
mentioned that it's in the it sounds
提到它在它的声音中
like it's in the interior corner so the
就像它在室内 角落那样
interior column being set up such a way
内部栏目正在 建立这样一种方式
that so you think of a building and if a
所以你想到一座建筑物， 如果一个
building with these trusses of wood and
用这些 木头和木头 建造
everything else and and built to look
一切，并建立 看看
nice if they flex
如果他们弯曲很好
like this then things start snapping
像这样， 事情就会开始爆发
things start breaking right so you get a
事情开始破裂， 所以你得到一个
trust structure made of steel tube that
信任结构由钢管的那
is like criss cross that is really
就像 是真正的 十字架
really solid that's not going to bend
真的很稳固，这不会弯曲
and warp and and flex the same way
并以相同的方式弯曲和弯曲
that's that traditional buildings like a
那就是像传统建筑一样
square building would in in that kind of
广场建筑将在那种
environment if there was an earthquake
环境如果发生地震
okay
好的
some may be worried about this sure
有些人可能会担心这个肯定
that's pretty tall for it but it is
这 对它来说 很高， 但它确实 很高
steel and wood right and I don't think
钢铁和木材的权利，我不 认为
I'm as worried in that tree seemed
我似乎很担心那棵树
pretty resilient like you see sure flex
像你看到的肯定弹性非常有弹性
in the wind right and yes are all right
在风中右转， 没错
with them I don't know if I live on the
与他们在一起， 我不知道我是否住在这里
top floor and I don't know that there
顶楼 ， 我不 知道 有
should be any amount of cooking inside
应该是里面的 任何烹饪量
building ever in case of fire yeah I
建设永远的情况下，是啊我
kind of want like what what kind of fire
有点想要 什么样的火
hazard is it to have a wooden structure
危险是它有一个木结构
of that magnitude that's right that's
这是正确的
giant like 350 meters that's half the
巨人像350米，这是一半
size a little more than half the height
尺寸 稍高于一半的高度
of the CN Tower that's crazy
加拿大国家电视塔的疯狂
this is significantly a non-smoking
这显然是不吸烟的
building you have to stand in the steel
建设你必须站在 钢铁
trusses you're fine I guess earthquakes
桁架你很好我猜地震
people but I'll match you got some
人， 但我会匹配你 有一些
issues researchers said Thursday that
研究人员周四表示
passports driver's licenses and other
护照驾驶执照等
sensitive documentation for thousands of
数以千计的敏感文档
FedEx customers were left online
联邦快递的客户已经上线
possibly for years in a blunder that
可能是多年的一个大错 那
left the information available to
留下可用的信息
identity thieves and other malicious
身份盗贼等 恶意
actors in all caram tech security Center
所有caram 技术安全 中心的演员
said researchers found 119 thousand
说研究人员发现119万
scanned documents stored in a publicly
公开存储扫描的文档
available Amazon s3 bucket the photo ID
可用亚马逊S3提供照片ID
scans were accompanied by completed US
扫描伴随着完成的美国
Postal Service forms that included names
包含姓名的邮政服务 表格
home addresses and phone numbers of
家庭住址和电话号码
people who requested to have mail
请求发送邮件的人
delivered by an authorized agent the IDS
由授权代理商 提供IDS
are from all over the world Mexico
来自世界各地的墨西哥
Canada European Union countries Saudi
加拿大欧盟国家沙特
Arabia Kuwait Japan Malaysia China
阿拉伯科威特日本马来西亚 中国
Australia and more the data was
澳大利亚和更多的数据是
Julie gathered by Bongo International a
邦戈国际公司聚集朱莉
company that helped North American
帮助北美的公司
retailers and brands sell online to
零售商和品牌在线销售
customers in other countries
其他国家的客户
FedEx acquired Bongo international in
联邦快递收购了邦戈国际
2014 and eventually changed its name to
2014年，并最终更名为
FedEx cross-border international FedEx
联邦快递跨境国际联邦快递
shut down the service last April the
关闭去年四月 服务
discovery of the customer IDs and other
发现客户ID和其他信息
personal information suggests that not
个人信息表明没有
only was the information never properly
只是 信息从未正确
secured to begin with but FedEx
担保开始但联邦快递
officials failed to purge the data once
官员未能清除数据一次
the service was discontinued Kron tech
该服务已停止使用Kron技术
said the information may have been
说可能是信息
available since 2009 people who used
自2009年以来可用的人
Bongo International or FedEx
邦戈国际或联邦快递
cross-border international should be on
跨境国际应该在
alert the incident incident is yet
提醒 事件事件尚未
another example of why people should
人们为什么 应该的 另一个例子
avoid giving over personal information
避免提供个人信息
whenever possible wow this is a weekly
只要有可能 哇， 这是一个每周一次
story when things feels like that's a
当事情感觉就像故事，这是一个
lot of now very like data you think
现在很多 很像你想的数据
about identity theft what do you need ID
关于身份盗窃你需要什么ID
up on an s3 bucket which is basically
基本上 是 一个S3的 桶
like a spot on the web to host files so
就像网络上的一个点来托管文件一样
right obviously they're able to download
显然他们能够下载
these hundreds of thousands of ID scans
这些数十万个ID扫描
right so it's ID and addresses and like
对，所以它的ID和地址等
it's actually everything you need to
它实际上是你需要的一切
become it if it was never secured to
如果它从未得到保护，就成为它
begin with yeah sounds like when FedEx
听起来像是当FedEx开始
took over the company why wouldn't you
接手公司你为什么不
purge like why wouldn't you get rid of
清除为什么你不会摆脱
that is it hidden from them in the
那是在他们隐藏的
acquisition of the company I have no
收购公司 我没有
idea like how can you not I don't know
想法， 你怎么能不我不知道
in an acquisition of that scale like
在 像 这样的规模收购
what if the here's a hypothetical for
如果这是一个假设的话
you what if they just didn't realize
如果他们没有意识到你会怎样
like they acquired the company and
像 他们收购了该公司 并
didn't realize that they were storing
没有意识到他们正在 储存
all this data unsafely I would assume
所有这些数据不安全， 我会假设
that they wouldn't have realized it that
他们不会意识到这一点
FedEx seems like an up-and-up sort of
联邦快递看起来像是一种新兴的类型
company that wouldn't do something like
公司不会做类似的事情
this intentionally
这是故意的
right like you yeah you would I guess in
右像你呀你将我 猜
crit would with that help encrypting yes
暴击会帮助加密是的
I have discussions with with people and
我与人和人讨论
I say what are you thinking
我说你在想什么
like you can't keep doing this you can't
就像你不能继续这样做你不能
not have a backup you can't have all of
没有备份，你不能拥有所有 的
your data stored on this onedrive you
你的数据存储在这个驱动器上
you know I'm I'm very vocal about hey
你知道我是我非常有声有关嘿
you need to have ransomware protection
你需要有勒索软件保护
on your Windows network yeah you can't
在你的Windows 网络上是的，你不能
just use antivirus anymore you can't use
只是使用 防病毒了，你不能使用
security essentials you have to have
您必须拥有的安全必备品
proper protection and whether they
适当的保护和他们是否
listen to me or not that's up to them
听我说或不听， 这取决于他们
now here's a case where did FedEx go in
现在这里是FedEx进入的情况
and did they see that that was there and
他们是否看到那是在那里？
did someone be vocal about it and say
有人对此发表了意见并说
you can't do this you can't have
你不能这样做， 你 不能 拥有
personal information freely available
个人信息免费提供
for anyone to download on s3 in a public
任何人 在公共场合下载s3
bucket I mean like think of a hard drive
我的意思是想像一个硬盘
that is accessible to anyone in the
这 是访问 的人
world don't know what this is and I've
世界 不 知道这是什么， 我已经
had that yeah I hear the sort of people
有，我 听到那种人
who should have had that hard drive in a
谁应该有 在该硬盘驱动器
landfill oh boy are you still holding on
垃圾填埋场哦，孩子 ， 你仍然持有
to Windows 7 well good news Microsoft
到Windows 7的 好消息微软
has back ported its Windows Defender
已经移植了它的Windows Defender
advanced threat protection security
高级威胁防护安全
toolkit from Windows 10 to Windows 7 and
从Windows 10到Windows 7和 Windows 7的工具包
8.1 now in hindsight looking back at our
8.1 事后 回顾我们的 看法
previous story I feel bad that I said
以前的故事我说我感觉不好
security essentials is not the product
安全要领 不是产品
for you I didn't see this coming but it
对你而言， 我并没有看到这一点，但它
was a perfect segue we realize that is
我们 意识到这是一个完美的阶段
now available perfect the release will
现在可用完美的发布意愿
allow those holding out with older
允许那些与年龄相符的人
versions of the operating system to get
要获取 的 操作系统 版本
the exploit and malware infection
利用和恶意软件感染
detection prevention and Event Reporting
检测预防和 事件报告
features offered by Windows 10 for
由Windows 10提供的功能
enterprises the extension to Windows 7
企业对Windows 7的扩展
and 8.1 will more importantly allow
8.1 会更重要的允许
admins to bring their older machines
管理员带来他们的旧机器
under the same security management and
在相同的安全管理下
administration tools they use for
他们使用的管理工具
Windows 10 pcs this is where Microsoft
Windows 10这是微软的地方
is focusing its pitch by adding ATP to
通过添加ATP来聚焦它的音高
Windows 7 and 8 point
Windows 7和 8点
Redmond hopes that it will convince sis
雷蒙德希望它能说服sis
admin's
admin的
to add those machines to the Windows
将这些机器添加到Windows
Defender monitoring systems that they
他们的 后卫监控系统
use for Windows 10 devices and in the
用于Windows 10设备和在Windows中
process product companies toward
加工产品公司
migrating in the older pcs to Windows 10
在较旧的PC中迁移到Windows 10
Microsoft noted that Windows 7 is still
微软指出，Windows 7 仍然是
slated for retirement in January of 2020
在2020年一月定为 退休
the software giant is also looking to
该软件巨头也在期待
extend the ATP support for non Windows
扩展非Windows的ATP支持
devices by signing up another partner
设备通过签署另一个合作伙伴
for its security push Sentinel 1 will be
因为其安全推送Sentinel 1将会
adding ATP support to the endpoint
为端点添加ATP支持
protection platform security tool it
保护平台安全工具吧
sells for Windows Mac Linux and VDI this
销售Windows Mac Linux和VDI
means that administrators can set up
意味着管理员可以设置
Sentinel 1 to automatically pass alerts
Sentinel 1自动传递警报
along to management consoles via ATP hmm
一起通过 ATP 管理控制台 嗯
I'm not a big Security Essentials fan I
我不是一个大的安全基础粉丝 我
like ESET I like proper protection but
像ESET 我喜欢适当的保护，但
for those who are going to opt for what
对于那些 谁是要 选择什么
comes with your computer it is good that
电脑配备的 这是件 好事
there's something a little more robust
还有一些 更强劲
than what's freely available right now
比现在的免费提供
yes if you're on Windows 7 why are you
是的，如果你在Windows 7 上，你为什么
on Windows 7 why are you on Windows yeah
在Windows 7 上，你为什么在Windows上呢？
I think a lot of people are still
我 想很多人还在
holding onto the past it's true and some
紧紧 抓住 过去的 这是真的，有些
people are stuck on hardware that
人们被困在硬件上
doesn't support Windows 10 or some
不支持 Windows 10或一些
people just don't want updates crippling
人们不 希望更新瘫痪
their computers right some people stop
他们的电脑让一些人 停下来
mullets she went there
她去了那里
big thanks to Roy W Nash in our
非常感谢我们的Roy W Nash
community of viewers for submitting
提交 观众群体
story to us this week thanks for
这个星期 给 我们的 故事 感谢
watching the category-five TV newsroom
看着五类 电视 新闻编辑室
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
不要忘记喜欢并订阅
all your tech news with a slight Linux
所有的技术新闻都有一个轻微的 Linux
bias and for more free content be sure
确保偏见和更多免费内容
to check out our website from the
从检查出我们的网站
category-five TV newsroom I'm Sasha
第五类电视新闻编辑室 我是Sasha
Rickman thanks Sasha this is category 5
里克曼感谢萨沙，这是第5类
technology TV and thank you so much for
技术电视和感谢你这么多
joining us a game this week I'm looking
本周我加入了我们的比赛
forward to seeing next week when we take
我们带着下周 去看看
this Plex Media Server and show you how
这Plex媒体服务器， 并告诉你如何
to actually import some of your video
实际进口一些您的视频
files and music and you
文件和 音乐 和 你
that system that we've now built on a
我们现在建立在一个系统上
Raspberry Pi three look forward to
树莓派三期待
seeing you next week
看到你 下周
take care I actually love everybody even
保重我 甚至爱每个人
if you have a Molly I feel bad
如果你有一个 莫莉我感觉不好
always nice to feel bad at the end of
总是很高兴在结束 时 感觉不好
the show
演出
[Music]
[音乐]